[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What brilliant American actor starred in the 2000 drama movie Cast Away?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks", "incorrect_answers": ["Leonardo DiCaprio", "Robert De Niro", "Tom Cruise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this film, high school student Max Fisher, played by Jason Schwartzman, is asked to use calculus to find the area of an ellipse.", "correct_answer": "Rushmore", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Novak", "Room 222", "The High School"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Star Trek: Insurrection, the Sona attempt to displace the Baku race from their homeworld, to take advantage of this special quality of the planet.", "correct_answer": "Regenerative radiation", "incorrect_answers": ["Self-replenishing natural resources", "Quick human development", "Unique Climate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Douglas Adams book The Hitchhikers Guide to the Galaxy, this number is the answer to the Ultimate Question of Life, the Universe and Everything.", "correct_answer": "42", "incorrect_answers": ["37", "53", "27"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The US bought Alaska in this year.", "correct_answer": "1867", "incorrect_answers": ["1942", "1882", "1854"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Acrophobia is a term, defined as an excessive fear of what?", "correct_answer": "Heights", "incorrect_answers": ["Travel", "Water", "Light"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the largest mollusk and the largest invertebrate in the world?", "correct_answer": "Colossal squid", "incorrect_answers": ["Giant African snail", "North Pacific Giant Octopus", "Giant squid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Martin Lewis Perl, Riccardo Giacconi, and Georges Charpak all received the Nobel Prize in ....?", "correct_answer": "Physics", "incorrect_answers": ["Literature", "Chemistry", "Medicine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin E is naturally soluble in this substance.", "correct_answer": "Fat", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Lactase", "Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the horror classic \u201cCarrie,\u201d Carries mom thinks that Carrie got her first period because she was sinning. She sends her off to go pray. What part of the house does Carrie get sent to?", "correct_answer": "The closet", "incorrect_answers": ["The den", "The basement", "The attic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of government does Sweden have?", "correct_answer": "Constitutional monarchy", "incorrect_answers": ["Absolute monarchy", "None of these", "Presidential republic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Popeyes go global?", "correct_answer": "1984", "incorrect_answers": ["1980", "1974", "1994"]}]